<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jonas Uekötter on Jonas</title><link>http://uekoetter.dev/</link><description>Recent content in Jonas Uekötter on Jonas</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://uekoetter.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>German companies using Flutter</title><link>http://uekoetter.dev/blog/german-flutter-companies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://uekoetter.dev/blog/german-flutter-companies/</guid><description>German companies using Flutter This listicle is about german companies using Flutter. Without further ado, lets go straight to them.
team neusta team neusta is a german holding with its headquater is in Bremen. They&amp;rsquo;re mostly doing consulting for other companies. Among its companies neusta infomantis and neusta mobile solutions are using Flutter. Neusta infomantis build, among other apps, the app for the local soccer club VfL Osnabrück. It&amp;rsquo;s available for Android and iOS.</description></item><item><title>My Flutter Packages</title><link>http://uekoetter.dev/blog/flutter_packages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://uekoetter.dev/blog/flutter_packages/</guid><description>My Flutter Packages I&amp;rsquo;ve created some nice libraries for Flutter.
Feedback feedback on pub.dev
This is a package which tries to make it really easy to gather feedback from your users. See here for more info.
Unleash unleash ob pub.dev
Unleash is a feature toggle service. My package is the recommended unofficial client for Dart as seen in the official repository.
Splash splash ob pub.dev
Splash is a collection of alternativ button clicked effects for Flutter.</description></item><item><title>Bookmarks</title><link>http://uekoetter.dev/bookmarks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://uekoetter.dev/bookmarks/</guid><description>Versioning Schemes CalVer SemVer Changelogs &amp;amp; Commits Keep-A-Changelog Conventional Changelog Conventional Comments (for reviews) Readmes Readme.so Make A Readme Dart&amp;rsquo;s guide on Readmes Design checklist.design Various Links career-ladders.dev What are different kinds of roles and what can you expect of them Dropbox Career Ladder TLDR legal Short explanations of various (software) licenses</description></item><item><title>Longboard Guide</title><link>http://uekoetter.dev/longboardguide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://uekoetter.dev/longboardguide/</guid><description>Policy Policy The App "Longboard Guide" does not collect any personal data. It collects crash reports, which cannot be used to identify a person.</description></item><item><title>Open Source Dashboard</title><link>http://uekoetter.dev/dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://uekoetter.dev/dashboard/</guid><description>Dashboard This is an overview over some of my open source software. It is primarily used by myself to get a better impression of its current status.
feedback version likes popularity pub points open pull requests open issues forks stars contributors watchers splash version likes popularity pub points open pull requests open issues forks stars contributors watchers unleash version likes popularity pub points open pull requests open issues forks stars contributors watchers screen recorder version likes popularity pub points open pull requests open issues forks stars contributors watchers application_icon version likes popularity pub points open pull requests open issues forks stars contributors watchers drawable version likes popularity pub points open pull requests open issues forks stars contributors watchers Other work Here is a list of software where I also contributed:</description></item><item><title>Sponsor</title><link>http://uekoetter.dev/donate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://uekoetter.dev/donate/</guid><description>Sponsor me I&amp;rsquo;m working on my packages on my free time, but I don&amp;rsquo;t have as much time as I would like to have. If the software I created is helping you, please consider to sponsor me. By doing so, you are really helping me out maintaining it. I&amp;rsquo;ll also prioritize your issues or your pull-requests before the others.
Thanks! I really appreciate your support.
Paypal | Buy me a coffee | GitHub Sponsor</description></item></channel></rss>